expopromoter.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy Policy - ExpoPromoter

ExpoPromoter is committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring you have a fruitful experience on our website. This privacy policy was created in order to explain you what information and why may be collected by ExpoPromoter and how it will be used and disclosed to our users.

All information relating the events dates and the location is subject to change. ExpoPromoter is not responsible for notifying its users about any amendments, so you may have to contact the events organizers for the updated information. 

This privacy policy covers following issues:

## What information and why we collect

While interacting with ExpoPromoter, you may be asked to fill in your personal data, including your full name, valid e-mail address, web site address, telephone, fax number, your company name, company department you are working in, your job position within this department. This information is needed to find out your interest area to ExpoPromoter and to maximize the feedback; and is processed when, for example, registering for the ExpoPromoter account and/or for our newsletter receiving. Sometimes, you will be also sent the information regarding the ExpoPromoter system modifications that is to a great importance for its users. 

The period of your personal data storage is determined by your personal appeal containing request of data erasure.

If you would like to access ExpoPromoter paid services section, we may have to collect your other appropriate information due to the billing purposes.

We also collect web usage information when web visitors access our web sites, including IP address, web pages visited on our web sites, time spent on our web pages, and return visits to our web sites. This data is aggregated and does not personally identify you. This information helps us to determine how to enhance our web sites and services. Aggregated information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any personally identifiable data about you or allow anyone to identify you individually. 

## How collected information is used

ExpoPromoter will not sell, rent or disclose in other way your information to the third parties. We will, as a fact, share only your non-personally identifiable data with our partners, advertisers and affiliates.

ExpoPromoter may share your information to conform the requirements of law or to defend the legal rights of ExpoPromoter.

ExpoPromoter also expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of its users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including ExpoPromoter partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy policies. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to the page, where certain content is actually created or hosted by a third party. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party. 

## How Cookies are used

ExpoPromoter uses cookies to store and sometimes track the information about you. It is employed to reduce the time spent by you while web-surfing and for effectiveness optimization. Cookies are small pieces of information that a web site sends to your computer for record-keeping purposes, which information is stored in a file on your computer. Anyways, you have always an option of blocking the cookies installation, but be aware that it may affect the functioning of our site's features. Cookies will not cause any damage and is not aimed at retrieving any personal data.

## Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information

You are always able to edit your ExpoPromoter account information by logging in and making the necessary modifications in the ExpoPromoter users' admin section. ExpoPromoter also saves your right to delete your data at any time and take it off from our data records. 

Additionally if you wish to send us request about your data rectification or total erasure (“right to be forgotten”) or providing you with your personal data or restriction of processing or regarding your data portability, please send an email to the following mailbox: [info@expopromoter.com](mailto:info@expopromoter.com). Our managers will contact you shortly after verifying your identity.

## Data security

Please note that your personal data is by default inaccessible to an indefinite number of natural persons without your personal intervention. To ensure that, we have implemented a number of technical and organisational measures.

## Changes to this privacy policy

ExpoPromoter may update this policy at any time. We are not responsible for notifying you about these changes, so please, check this page of our site periodically.
